http://www.tennsco.com/privacy

COVID-19 UPDATE
Tennsco recognizes the immense impact the COVID-19 pandemic is having on our country and throughout the world. As an Essential Business, we
continue to manufacture and ship all products, while keeping the health and safety of our employees, customers and partners our top priority.
We are here for you, welcome your calls, and are happy to assist in any way we can.
Products are made and shipped from Dickson, TN.
VIEW ourProductCatalog
LEARN more about our Quick Ship program for faster delivery
Privacy Statement
Tennsco respects your privacy and our site visitors information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.
Information Collected If you request or submit information to us by sending an Email via info@tennsco.com or by filling out a "contact" form, we may save your Email address as well as any other information you provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, Email, or phone to convey information about our solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your Email and other information will not be sold to any third party.
Information Collected by Others This notice addresses only Tennsco's website policy, and does not apply to sites that users access via links from our site. Tennsco is not responsible for the information collecting policies of other sites, for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, or for the information or content contained therein. Often, links to other websites are provided solely on the basis that they may contain useful information for our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.
Cookies Tennsco's website does not use cookies.
Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information If you would like to have your personal information removed from our records, please send an Email with "Remove personal information" in the subject line.
Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information Tennsco may disclose information when legally compelled to do so: when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so or for the protection of our legal rights.
Periodic Policy Changes Please note that Tennsco reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.
This policy statement is made in the name of Tennsco and is effective as of November 21, 2012. This statement does not create an agreement between Tennsco and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.
Contact Us:
Tennsco 201 Tennsco Drive P.O. Box 1888 Dickson, TN 37056-1888
Corporate Office: 615.446.8000 Toll-Free: 800.251.8184 Customer Service: 866.446.8686 Fax: 800.722.0134 Email: info@tennsco.com
